准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
强人俱乐部
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
欢迎来到酷乐湖
啊  酷乐湖
Ah, Goo Lagoon
有沙有海的风水宝地
a luxurious oasis of sand and sea
真是的  海绵宝宝
Shoot, SpongeBob
你穿衬衫打领带还怎么游泳
how can we go swimming when you're in a shirt and tie?
确实  我真傻
Yes, how foolish of me
就听你的马上整改
Allow me to remedy said situation right now
我就到这间更衣篷
I will just use this changing tent here
去换泳装
to change into my bathing suit
不会偷偷摸摸做别的勾当
And I won't do anything else
海绵宝宝表现得大惊小怪得不得了
SpongeBob's acting jumpier
than a rattlesnake in a pickle barrel
等等
Wait
什么
what?
衣服换归换
I'll be changing all right
但不换泳装
but not into a bathing suit
等着让珊迪瞧瞧
Wait until Sandy sees
我带来了空手道装备
that I brought my karate gear
珊迪这回肯定打败不了我
Sandy won't beat me this time
因为我坐拥必胜的要素
because I've got the element on my side
出其不意
The element of surprise
海绵宝宝  你准备好了吗
SpongeBob, are you ready?
没错  珊迪
Yes, Sandy
我准备好了
I most certainly am ready
准备嗨起来
Ready to get it on
你看吧  海绵宝宝
Look, SpongeBob
我也带来了空手道装备
we both brought our karate gear
看来英雄所见略同
Great minds think alike, I suppose
我可能是倒下了  但我还没放弃
I may be down, but I'm not out
你做得好啊
Way to go, buddy
那个土豆沙拉三天才做好
It took us three days to make that potato salad
三天
Three days
珊迪
Sandy?
我是珊迪没错
I'm Sandy all right
就在沙底
I'm very sandy
我听懂了
I get it
她叫珊迪
She's "Sandy"
她名字跟沙底谐音
That's her name and she's also covered in
没错
yes
冰淇淋
在德克萨斯老家
Back in Texas
大家都管冰淇淋叫冻牛奶
we call ice cream "frozen cow juice"
先失陪一下
Excuse me for a sec
谢谢你
Thank you
不对  是谢谢你
No, no, thank you
谁朝我扔纸
Who threw that piece of paper at me?
大家排队干什么
What's everyone waiting in line for?
美女  这是进强人俱乐部的队伍
Ahoy, fair lass, it be the line
to get into the Salty Spitoon
强人俱乐部
七大洋有史以来最强人的水手俱乐部
the roughest, toughest, sailor club
ever to be built under the seven seas
只有最坏的恶霸才进得去
Only the baddest of the bad can get in
你得有肌肉
You need to have muscles
肌肉上也得有肌肉
You need to have muscles on your muscles
眼球上也得有肌肉
You need to have muscles on your eyeballs
看来可以进去玩个尽兴了  海绵宝宝
Looks like a rip-snortin' good time, SpongeBob
对啊  咱们进去吧
Yeah, let's go in
请进
Go ahead
欢迎光临强人俱乐部
Welcome to the Salty Spitoon
你有多强
How tough are ya?
我有多强
How tough am I?
我早餐吃了一碗钉子
I had a bowl of nails for breakfast this morning
那又怎样
Yeah, so?
没配牛奶
Without any milk
这边请
Right this way
抱歉让你们久等了
Sorry to keep you waiting
欢迎光临强人俱乐部
Welcome to the Salty Spitoon
妈
你有多强
How tough are ya?
我有多强
How tough am I?
哇
Wow
还有没有纹身
Got any more tattoos?
没那个必要
That won't be necessary
请进
Go ahead
谢了
Thanks
里面见  海绵宝宝
See ya inside, SpongeBob
你有多强
How tough are ya?
我有多强
How tough am I?
你有新买的未开封番茄酱吗
You got a new bottle of ketchup?
有
Sure
看我的
It's on
要是能用热水冲一下
If I could just run this under some hot water
请走吧
Get outta here
这地方对你来说太强了  小家伙
This place is too tough for you, little man
对我来说太强了
Too tough for me?
一点道理也没有
That's downright ridiculous
跟你说
I'll have you know
上周我给香料园胶水  踢到脚趾
I stubbed my toe last week
while watering my spice garden
只哭了二十分钟
and I only cried for 20 minutes
跟你说  小朋友
Listen, kid
你到那边应该舒服点
I think you'd be more comfortable over at that place
儿童乐园
Weenie Hut Jr's?
你是说我只能去儿童乐园吗
Are you saying I belong at Weenie Hut Jr's?
不对  抱歉
Oh, no, sorry
我其实是在指隔壁那家
I was actually pointing to the place next to it
婴儿宝宝乐园
Super Weenie Hut Jr's?
对
Yeah
除非你觉得自己够强  能打败我
Unless you think you're tough enough to fight me
儿童乐园
你的收藏进度如何
How's your collection coming along?
不是我故意吹牛
Well I don't mean to brag
进度可乐观了
but it's pretty sweet
我现在要入手第347册
I'm in the process of acquiring issue 347
这样我就能集齐第四套了
which will give me my fourth complete set
不会吧
No
一群小屁孩
What weenies
真是的
Oh, brother
你想再来一杯加柠檬皮的无糖可乐吗
Would you care for another diet cola with a lemon twist
小屁孩
Weenie?
什么
What?
可我不是小屁孩
But I'm not a weenie
很抱歉  先生
I'm sorry, sir
我的传感器显示  你就是小屁孩
but my sensors indicate that you are indeed a weenie
是
根本不可能
That's impossible
内心是隐藏不了的
You can't hide what's inside
我要求进入你们的俱乐部
I demand entrance into your club
理由是  我不是小屁孩
on the grounds that I am not a weenie
雷吉  怎么样了
Hey, Reg, how's it going?
刚说到哪了
You were saying?
请进吧
Go ahead, buddy
谢了  雷吉
Thanks, Reg
原来你叫雷吉
So, your name's Reg?
你能不能给我走开
Would you get outta here?
听好了  雷吉
Mark my words, Reg
我一定进得去强人俱乐部
I will get into the Salty Spitoon
一定
I will
进不去是吧
Couldn't get in, huh?
你需要的正是强人的发型
What you need is a tough hairdo
强人俱乐部得有强人的发型才能进去
No one gets into the double-S without a tough hairdo
我不同意
I disagree
我看到有个秃头进去了
I saw a guy going in there and he was bald
我见过那位
I saw that guy
他那不算秃头  是剃了光头
He wasn't bald, he had a shaved head
剃光头
Shaved
那也算发型
that's a hairdo
结案
Case closed
他去哪了
Where'd he go?
我想他说要去假发店什么的
I believe he said something
about going to the wig store
将军
Check and mate
近来可好  大哥
What's shaking, my man?
没啥事
Not much
我先前有见过你吗
Say, haven't I seen you before?
不见得
Doubt it
我漂泊在外
I'm a drifter
正好漂来这座小镇
Just blew into town
听说你家俱乐部挺强人的
Heard your club was pretty tough
就想过来瞧瞧
Thought I'd check it out
你想得美
Nice try, kid
我知道是你
I know it's you
你在胡说什么
What are you talking about?
大家好  有什么事情
Hey everybody, what's going on?
请进吧
You can go in
非常抱歉
Sorry about that
你想干什么
And what do you want?
请让我进去你们的俱乐部吧
I'd like to gain entrance to your social club, please
我的发型肯定没问题
I believe my hairdo is in order
所以你支持秃头派还是剃头派
So where do you stand
on the whole bald vs. shaved debate?
雷吉
Hey-ya, Reg
你来了才热闹
All right, now it's a party
对了  你新纹了身啊
Oh, yeah, check out the new ink
谢谢
Thanks
看我拿它变花样
Look what I can make it do
不错嘛
Yeah
那个能变什么花样
What about that one?
话说我不记得纹过这个
You know, I don't remember getting this one
你能让它跳舞吗
Can you make it dance?
我来试试看
Here, let me try
先等一下
Wait a minute
请进
Go ahead in
很好  雷吉
Yeah, sure, Reg
谢谢
Thanks
休想进去  小家伙
Nice try, little man
我刚排在你前面
I was in front of you
才没有
No, you weren't
你说我骗你吗
Are you callin' me a liar?
是又怎么样
I ain't callin' you for dinner
你们两个别打了
Hold it, you two
打住
That's enough
你们两个都很强
You're both plenty tough
请进
Go ahead in
好
All right
谢了  雷吉
Thanks, Reg
那我呢
What about me?
我也跟着一起打了
I was in that scrap
我看到你逃跑了
I saw you running
等你真打再说
When you get in a real fight, then we'll talk
那就是时候要更上一层楼了
Well then, I guess it's time to take it up a notch
要再来一份圣代吗  小屁孩
Care for another sundae, weenie?
我不是小屁孩
I am not a weenie
别急  大家都是朋友
Relax, you're among friends
我朋友才不来儿童乐园
My friends don't hang out at Weenie Hut Jr's
这倒是  海绵宝宝
You tell 'em, SpongeBob
派大星  你来干什么
Patrick, what are you doing here?
我双童周三都会来
I'm always here on Double-Weenie Wednesday
其实双童周三现在变周五了
Actually, they moved
Double-Weenie Wednesday to Friday
而且今天是周一
Besides, today's Monday
原来今天是超童周一啊
So it's Mega-Weenie Monday?
现在那是周天的活动
That's now on Sunday
真见鬼
Barnacles
婴儿宝宝乐园有超童周一
Super Weenie Hut Jr's has a Mega-Weenie Monday
不对  你那是怪童周一
No, you're thinking of Monster-Weenie Monday
我没空争这个
I don't have time for this
我要去跟不熟的肌肉男找茬打架
I've gotta go pick a fight with a muscular stranger
只有这样才能进强人俱乐部
It's the only way of getting into the Salty Spitoon
海绵宝宝  这样不行
No, SpongeBob, you can't
太危险了
It's too dangerous
根本没得选
I've got no choice
我有个建议
I have a suggestion
不然就假打
Why not fake a fight?
这个办法好
That's not a bad idea
你可以拿外号骂我
You can call me a couple of bad names
我们就打起来  然后就能
we rumble, next thing you know
顺理成章让你进强人俱乐部了
you're in the Salty Spitoon
好像也没多大代价
Well, I guess I've got nothing to lose
就这么办
Let's do it
好耶
Yeah
你怎么就没法帮我们解决问题
How come you never help us with our problems?
我是机器人  不会专门制造奇迹
I am a robot, not a miracle worker
午安  雷吉
Afternoon, Reg
慢着  小家伙
Whoa, whoa, little man
你还是不能进
You still can't go in
那真是气死我了
Well, that makes me pretty mad
是吗
Oh, yeah?
是啊
Yeah
我得去打个谁
I might have to beat someone up
才能浇灭心中的无名业火
just to get rid of all this blind fury
我为不顺眼的那位深表遗憾
I feel pretty sorry
for the next guy who looks at me funny
那位怎么说
What about that guy?
我
I
别傻了
don't be silly
他又没惹到谁
he's not bothering anybody
我是说  不像
I mean, not like
那位
that guy
谁  我吗
Who, me?
对  就你
Yeah, you
光站着嬉皮笑脸的
Standing there all smiling and whatnot
你得多学学礼貌
Somebody ought to teach you some manners
好  可我得警告你
Okay, but I must warn you
我刚好是世界冠军级
I happen to be a world championship
搏击选手
"kick box er"
不管你是不是戴维琼斯的魔种
I don't care if you're the demon seed of Davey Jones
你都得下地狱去  胖墩
You're going down, Tubby
胖墩
Tubby?
不准叫我胖墩
Nobody calls me Tubby
等等  派大星
Wait, Patrick
你应该要让我赢的  记得吗
You're supposed to let me win, remember?
啊对
Oh, yeah
不要  手下留情
No, please wait
不要  求你饶了我吧
No, please, have mercy
你连碰都没碰就把他打得落花流水
You destroyed that guy without even touching him
是吗
I did?
从来没想过我会这么说  但是
I never thought I'd say this, but
请进吧
go ahead in
真的吗
Really?
我能进去了
I can go in?
我的天啊  没想到这一刻会到来
Oh, my gosh, I never thought this moment would come
我  海绵宝宝
I, SpongeBob SquarePants
已经够强  可以进强人俱乐部了
am tough enough to get into the Salty Spitoon
今天是我一生中最快乐的一天
This is the happiest day of my life
珊迪
Sandy?
怎么回事
What happened?
你冲进门  踩到冰块滑倒了
You ran inside and slipped on an ice cube
医院
急诊
怎么回事
What happened?
我踩到冰块滑倒了
I slipped on an ice cube
身上都是伤  害我好痛痛
and got covered in boo-boos
痛痛是吗
Boo-boos, eh?
应该去那家医院
I think you guys want that hospital
儿童综合医院
Weenie Hut General?
章鱼威廉回来了
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜总监
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
十
Ten
蟹堡王
九
nine
八
eight
七
seven
六
six
五
five
四
four
三
three
二
two
一
one
我不干了  蟹老板
I'm done with my shift, Mr. Krabs
容我发言
And let me just say
我终有一天会功成名就
there will come a day
when I will make something of my life
再也不用踏进这家小破店
and I will never have to
set foot in this grease trap again
说得好
Yeah
午休之后再见  章鱼哥
we'll see you after your lunch break, Squidward
好
Okay
所以我就坐我的私人快艇
So I just took my private yacht
渡过了我的私人大湖
across my private lake
抵达了我的私人机场
to my private heliport
我的私人小岛只能坐飞机离开
It's the only way off my private island
完蛋了
Oh, shrimp
是我高中的死对头  章鱼威廉
It's my arch rival from high school, Squilliam Fancyson
不能让他看到我穿着蟹堡王的制服
I can't let him see me in my Krusty Krab uniform
你是在午休吗  章鱼哥
On your lunch break, eh, Squiddy?
对
Yes
我是说不对
I mean no
我是说
I mean
你近来可好
Whatcha been up to?
就是你失败的事情我全在成功
Just succeeding in everything you've failed in
你也没多了不起嘛  章鱼威廉
You are no great shakes, Squilliam Fancyson
谁都能在裤头村这种穷乡僻壤发迹
Anyone can be a big shot
in a hick town like Bikini Bottom
是这样吗
Is that so?
那就说说你高中毕业以来有何高就吧
Let's hear what you've accomplished
since high school, Squiddy
千万别怕  章鱼哥
Don't be intimidated, Squidward
想象他只穿内裤的样子
Try to imagine him in his underwear
不会吧  他身材真好
Oh, no, he's hot
我从事的是
I'm, uh, in
餐饮行业
food service
等一下  你该不会是
Hold it, don't tell me
在当收银员吧
You're a cashier
别说谎
Don't lie
说谎更容易完蛋
Lying always makes it worse
我坐拥一家五星级餐厅
I own a five-star restaurant
章鱼哥  我都不知道你会这么成功
Squidward, I had no idea you were such a success
没错
That's right
能让我来参观你餐厅  我将不胜荣幸
And I would be honored
if you would allow me to come to your restaurant
就在今晚
tonight
今晚
T-t-t-t-t-t-tonight?
大家都要一起来
In fact, we'll all come
我请客
My treat
拜托  蟹老板
Please, Mr. Krabs
一定要救救我
you got to help me
等他们今晚来参观
When they get here tonight
肯定都看得出来我是大骗子加大废物
they'll see I'm just a big phony and a loser
好想哭
Boo-hoo
就用世界最小的小提琴为你奏悲歌吧
Let me play a sad song for you
on the world's smallest violin
我没开玩笑
This is serious
我知道
I know
这真的是全世界最小的小提琴
this really is the world's smallest violin
看吧
See?
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
求你让我经营一下餐厅
Please let me run the restaurant
一晚就好
for just one night
我真的需要让章鱼威廉大开眼界
I really need to impress Squilliam
章章章  章鱼威廉
Sq-Sq-Sq-Squilliam?
就那个
That guy
活在你的梦想里还赚了好几百万那位
who made millions doing what you wish you could do?
别往伤口撒盐
Don't rub it in
你怎么不早说
Why didn't you tell me?
我们这就打败他
We'll take him to the cleaners
都听好了
All right, listen up
章鱼威廉再二十分钟就要到了
Men, Squilliam Fancyson will be here in 20 minutes
因此  我们要把蟹堡王
Therefore, we need to turn the Krusty Krab
尽快变成高档餐厅
into a fancy restaurant as soon as possible
派大星  你来干什么
Patrick, what are you doing here?
军团可以让我生活更美好  长官
I thought the Corps would straighten out my life, sir
军团
The Corps?
怎么
What the?
派大星  这又不是
Patrick this isn't the
也没得选了
Beggars can't be choosers
你会端庄大方地拿客人帽子吗
Can you take hats
in a dignified and sophisticated manner?
是要像娘娘腔那样吗
You mean like a weenie?
好啊
Okay
帽子给我好吗  先生
May I take your hat, sir?
帽子
May I
行了  我听够了
All right, I've heard enough
任务交给你
You've got the job
蟹老板  你先前在美食号服务过是吧
Mr. Krabs, didn't you once serve on the S.S. Gourmet?
没错
Aye-aye
那就让你当大厨
Then you'll be our chef
我可以干什么
What can I do?
我居然会这么说
I can't believe I'm saying this
但是  海绵宝宝
but, SpongeBob
你来担任服务生
you're going to have to be the waiter
那是什么
What's that?
得负责走到桌前接单
It's the guy who goes to tables and takes orders
其他餐厅是这样的吗
Do other restaurants do that?
没错  就这样
Yes, they do that
听好了  章鱼威廉已经上路了
Now listen, Squilliam is on his way
你就只剩二十分钟不到的时间
and you have less than 20 minutes
速成高档餐厅服务生
to become a fancy waiter
所以你就看这本
so read this
二十分钟不到速成高档餐厅服务生
"How To Become a Fancy Waiter in Less Than 20 Minutes"
你放心  章鱼哥
Don't worry, Squidward
我会记下每一页
I'll memorize every page
一个标点符号都不落下
Right down to the punctuation mark
行  职位都安排好了
All right, I've got all the positions filled
估计能成功了
I just might pull this off
帽子给我
Give me that hat
都说了快给我
I said give it to me
你到底交不交出来
Are you going to hand it over or not?
不许给我顶嘴
Don't you back-sass me
他不过就保管个帽子而已
He's just the hat-check guy
才没多大必要
nothing essential
怎么了
What happened?
啥东西
What is it?
豆子
Peas
豆
传统古法制作
Made 'em the old-fashioned way
蟹老板  把那玩意给我扔出
Mr. Krabs, you got to take them out of the
我的老天爷  这什么东西
Holy fish paste, what is that?
那是开胃菜
That's the appetizer
可你不是说
But, I thought you said
你是美食号上的主厨吗
you were the head chef on the S.S. Gourmet?
有说过吗
Did I say that?
才没有  我在美食号是扫厕所的
No, I cleaned the bathrooms on the Gourmet
我是拉肚子号的主厨
I was the head chef on the S.S. Diarrhea
你在这啊
There you are
海绵宝宝  一定要救救我
SpongeBob, you got to help me
派大星跟蟹老板不靠谱
Patrick and Mr. Krabs aren't working out
而且章鱼威廉就快到了
and Squilliam's almost here
而且  而且
and, and
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob?
我做不到
I can't do it
我做不到  章鱼哥
I can't do it, Squidward
什么
What?
每句  每段
Every sentence, every paragraph
勺子
Spoons
面包
Bread
沙拉
Salad
辣椒
Pepper
你还不懂吗
Don't you understand?
我脑子快塞爆了
My brain is full to bursting
要是再让我记客人点的菜
If I have to memorize a single order
我就真要爆炸了
I think I'm going to explode
海绵宝宝  先撑着
SpongeBob, hold on
来放松个一秒钟
Let's just take a second here to relax
再放松
Little more
好
Good
现在
Now
我要你脑袋放空
I want you to empty your mind
放空我脑袋
Empty my mind?
放空你脑袋
Empty your mind
放空我脑袋
Empty my mind
抛开心中一切杂念
Empty your mind of everything
忘掉跟高级餐饮服务无关的一切
that doesn't have to do with fine dining
只记得高级餐饮服务  还有呼吸
Fine dining and breathing
刚刚收到老大的命令
Just got an order from the boss
把跟高级餐饮服务无关的一切全扔了
dump everything that isn't about fine dining
全扔了
Everything?
Everything
快点快点
Come on, come on
动作快动作快
Quicker, quicker
捉水母
开始扔掉开始扔掉
Start dumping, start dumping
童年回忆
香料种植
小窍门
快点  加快动作
Come on, let's get moving
别磨蹭
Hurry up
我付你工资是叫你来干嘛的
What am I paying you for?
你又没付我工资
You don't pay me
我们都不存在
We don't even exist
我们就只是个具象化的精巧比喻
We're just a clever visual metaphor
把抽象的思想概念拟人化了
used to personify the abstract concept of thought
再插科打诨就别干了
One more crack like that and you're out of here
不要  求你了
No, please
我家有三个小孩要养
I have three kids
数学
感觉怎么样
How do you feel?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob?
根本没用
This isn't working
我得去找章鱼威廉多争取点时间
I gotta go tell Squilliam I need more time
只要去找章鱼威廉跟他说
I'll just go to Squilliam and tell him and
章鱼威廉  你来了
Squilliam, you're here
你好啊  章鱼哥
Hello, Squiddy
咱都准备好被你的五星级餐厅迷倒了
We're all ready to be dazzled
by your five-star restaurant
等等  章鱼威廉
Wait, Squilliam
我得向你解释
I've got to explain
解释什么
Explain what?
你  章鱼哥
That you, Squidward Tentacles
高中公认最容易班门弄斧的那位
voted most likely to suck eggs in high school
要把一个破烂汉堡摊子办成五星级
are trying to pass off
a lousy burger stand as a five-star
餐厅
restaurant?
啊这啊这
Hommina, hommina
啊这要来就餐吗
Table for Hommina?
我立刻让你们就座
I can seat you immediately
你都是怎么做到的
How did you do all this?
很简单
It was easy
放空脑袋就行了
once I cleared my mind
可蟹老板跟派大星呢
But what about Krabs and Patrick?
妥善安排好了
Taken care of
这边请
Right this way, please
晚上好  先生
Good evening, sir
为您推荐今晚菜单中的蟹黄新堡
From our menu tonight
菜单
might I recommend the Krabby Newburg?
选用最优质的陈年进口海草
We take the finest cuts of aged, imported kelp
以园中的药草加以填充
stuff them with herbs from our garden
用羊皮纸包好
wrap them in parchment
配上斩获过大奖的香葱橄榄酱
with our award-winning shallot tapenade
于柴火陶制烤炉中慢烤六小时
slow-roast them for six hours
in our wood-fired, clay-filled oven, or kiva
最后再用稍煮的珊瑚点缀
and serve them with a garnish of wilted coral
放上红木板为你献上
on a mahogany plank
真是妙极了
This is fantastic
谢谢  先生
Thank you, sir
掐我一把  我一定是在做梦
Pinch me, I must be dreaming
如果还有需要  随时叫我
If you need anything else, just call
海绵宝宝  真谢谢你所做的一切
SpongeBob, I can't thank you enough for all you're doing
我只会高级餐饮服务和呼吸
Fine dining and breathing are all I know how to do
成功了
It worked
真不敢相信
I can't believe it
章鱼威廉真以为我坐拥五星级餐厅
Squilliam thinks I own a five-star restaurant
该来火上浇油了
Time to rub it in his face
章鱼威廉  我等着呢
Well, Squilliam, I'm waiting
我都承认了
All right, I admit it
全都堪称一绝
Everything is fabulous
食物  气氛
The food, the atmosphere
完美无缺
Everything's flawless
这样的话  请你念下这个
In that case, I need you to read this
章鱼哥
"Squidward Tentacles"
而且还要戴上这个
And I need you to wear this
章鱼哥第一
章鱼哥坐拥全
"Squidward Tentacles has the fanciest"
抱歉  再念一遍
I'm sorry, one more time
章鱼哥坐拥全裤头村最高档的餐厅
"Squidward Tentacles
has the fanciest restaurant in Bikini Bottom
而且他没有班门弄斧
and he does not suck eggs"
章鱼哥  不得不说
Squidward, I must tell you
谢谢你
Thank you
真正让我折服的是你的优秀服务生
What really won me over was your brilliant waiter
就好像
It's as if
他只会高级餐饮服务和呼吸一样
all he knows is fine dining and breathing
我一定要知道你的名字
I must know your name
我的名字
My name?
没错  就是你的名字
Yes, your name, son
惠灵顿牛肉
Beef Wellington?
不对  你的名字
No, your name
叉子放左边
The fork on the left?
别搞笑了
Stop joking
名字告诉他
Tell him your name
我的名字
My name
什么名字
What's his name?
根本没有名字
I got nothing on a name
快啊  名字是什么
Come on baby, what's the name?
我们把他名字扔了
We threw out his name
非常抱歉
I am so very sorry
我不知道他是中了什么
I don't know what has gotten into that
胳肢窝要再来点汤吗
More soup for your armpits?
用餐愉快
Please enjoy the food
上面还要再加点奶酪吗  先生
Would you like some cheese on that, sir?
不要
No, no
大家快逃  开胃菜来了
Run for your lives, everyone, it's the appetizer
章鱼哥  收银员
章鱼哥  我等着呢
Well, Squiddy, I'm waiting
我都承认了
Okay, I admit it
我是个骗子
I'm a fraud
我搞了这可悲徒劳的一出
This was all a futile, pathetic attempt
就想让你大开眼界
to impress you
这并不是我的餐厅
This isn't really my restaurant
我只是个收银员
I'm just a cashier
章鱼哥  我能理解
Squidward, I understand
我也有话想跟你坦白
I have a confession to make myself
我的大好生活都是瞎编的
I made everything up about my life
我没快艇  喷气机什么的
I have no yachts, jets or anything
我只想让你大开眼界
I was only trying to impress you
糟糕可悲的事实就是
The horrible, sad truth is
我也是个收银员
I'm a cashier, too
真的吗
Is that true?
当然是假的
Of course not
我富得流油
I'm filthy, stinking rich
大家走吧
Come on, everyone
来坐坐我的热气球赌场
Let's all take a ride in my balloon/casino
万岁
Hooray
我头好疼啊
I got such a headache
你又怎么了
What's going on with you?
老样子
The usual
能不能给我滚
Would you get out of here